A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Leadership Development Program, Administrative Files FA650
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, Leadership Development Program, Administrative Files
1966-1977
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation
FA650
11.68 Cubic Feet
Conditions Governing Access note
Material is open for scholarly research, with prior archival review.
Material more than ten years old is open for scholarly research.
Select individual files are restricted, as noted. Permission to access these files must be obtained from the Ford Foundation before scholarly access is permitted.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Ford Foundation archive was deposited at RAC in 2011. Ford Foundation records, correspondence, reports, program files and officers papers were transferred to, and accessioned by, RAC beginning in 2011. Accessions continue as necessary.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be restricted from scholarly research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment. Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be restricted from scholarly research at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/RAC Head of Reference.
Separated Materials
Appendix A: Reports – Unpublished reports written by Ford Foundation staff and consultants were removed from their original folders, scanned and transferred to the Archives' collection of staff and consultant reports. See Appendix A for a list of these reports and their specific assigned number. The reports are listed in alphabetical order by author. The assigned number may be used to access reports in the online catalog.
Ford Foundation
- Northeast Region, 1966-1975; I
  - Northeast Region Administrative Correspondence, 1967-1975; I.1
    - A, 1967-1971 (Box 1)
    - B, 1967-1974 (Box 1)
    - Bohrson, Ralph, 1971-1974 (Box 1)
    - Bohrson, Ralph G., Jul 1967-Jul 1968 (Box 1)
    - Bohrson, Ralph G., Jul 1968-May 1969 (Box 1)
    - Bohrson, Ralph G. (1/2), Jun 1969-Jun 1971 (Box 1)
    - Bohrson, Ralph G. (2/2), Jun 1969-Jun 1971 (Box 1)
    - Bohrson, Ralph G., Jul 1971-Jun 1972 (Box 1)
    - C, 1967-1974 (Box 1)
    - Chavis, K.C. (K.Z.), 1968-1975 (Box 1)
    - D, 1967-1972 (Box 1)
    - Dennis, Nancy, 1968-1974 (Box 1)
    - Derrer, Doug, 1969-1973 (Box 1)
    - E, 1967-1973 (Box 1)
    - F, 1967-1974 (Box 1)
    - Feldman, Sheryl and George Mitchell Re: George Mitchell for Governor, 1974 (Box 1)
    - G, 1967-1971 (Box 1)
    - Goethals, George, 1967-1969 (Box 1)
    - Grant, David, 1969-1974 (Box 1)
    - Grant, David, 1967-1969 (Box 1)
    - H, 1967-1974 (Box 1)
    - Hillman, Mary "Sue", 1973-1974 (Box 1)
    - Hinckley, Edward -- Re: Indian Affairs, 1968-1975 (Box 1)
    - I, 1967-1971 (Box 1)
    - J, 1967-1974 (Box 1)
    - K, 1967-1974 (Box 1)
    - Kemsley, Bill, 1967-1973 (Box 1)
    - L, 1967-1974 (Box 2)
    - Leimenstoll, Marilyn -- Shelburne, Vermont, 1970-1973 (Box 2)
    - Lotz, Jim (1/2), 1967-1973 (Box 2)
    - Lotz, Jim (2/2), 1967-1973 (Box 2)
    - Love, Robert -- Dean, University of New Brunswick, 1968-1972 (Box 2)
    - M, 1967-1972 (Box 2)
    - Manzer, Murray H., 1968-1970 (Box 2)
    - Mc, 1967-1974 (Box 2)
    - Moll, C.L., 1967-1969 (Box 2)
    - N, 1967-1974 (Box 2)
    - Nachtigal, Paul, 1969-1973 (Box 2)
    - Newman, Brenda, 1970-1972 (Box 2)
    - Nicholas, Andrew, 1969-1972 (Box 2)
    - O, 1967-1974 (Box 2)
    - P, 1967-1971 (Box 2)
    - Perley, Ivan Sr. -- LDP Proposal and Consultant Work -- Maliseet, New Brunswick, 1970-1972 (Box 2)
    - Q (Paul Quimby), 1967-1969 (Box 2)
    - R, 1967-1974 (Box 2)
    - Rafferty, Mary Patricia, 1972-1975 (Box 2)
    - S, 1967-1974 (Box 2)
    - T, 1967-1972 (Box 2)
    - U, V, 1967-1972 (Box 2)
    - W, 1967-1974 (Box 2)
    - X, Y, Z, 1967-1972 (Box 2)
    - Community Development -- Upward Bound and Community Action, 1968 (Box 2)
    - Indians -- International Indian Independent School Bulletin, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
    - Educational Programming -- Educating Administrators for Education, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Fellows -- Bourgeois, Charles, Grand-Digue, New Brunswick [RESTRICTED], 1969-1970 (Box 2)
    - Fellows -- Somers, Melvin -- Grant File [RESTRICTED], 1969-1973 (Box 2)
    - Fellows -- Spearin, Jean, Woodland, Maine [RESTRICTED], 1970-1971 (Box 2)
    - Fellows -- White, Nancy C., New Hampshire -- Grant File [RESTRICTED], 1968-1969 (Box 2)
    - New Brunswick, 1967-1970 (Box 2)
    - Statistics -- 1974 Conference Questionnaires (Box 2)
    - Statistics -- December Statistics Re: LDP Fellows (1967-1968 season) (Box 2)
    - Statistics -- Leadership Fellows Program Box Score -- Progress Report, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Statistics -- New York Trip Re: LDP Planning, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Statistics -- Past Fellows Region/Community Statistics, 1971-1973 (Box 2)
    - Statistics -- Recruiting Statistics, 1971-1973 (Box 2)
    - Statistics -- Statistics Re: Individual Awards, Program Costs, 1968-1971 (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous -- Dinner Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous -- Evaluation Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous -- History of Leadership Development Program -- Brochures, Application Instructions, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Northeast Region Administrative Files by Fellowship Season, 1967-1975; I.2
    - Briggs, H. Peter, 1968-1969 (Box 3)
    - General Office Correspondence (second year), 1968 (Box 3)
    - General Office Correspondence (Northeast), 1968-1969 (Box 3)
    - Correspondence Re: Fellows (Northeast), 1967-1969 (Box 3)
    - Selection Committee (Northeast), 1967-1968 (Box 3)
    - Staff (Northeast), 1968 (Box 3)
    - New York Office Administrative Correspondence and Information, 1970-1971 Season -- General Office Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 3)
    - New York Office Administrative Correspondence and Information, 1970-1971 Season -- Consultants (includes Selection Committee), 1969-1970 (Box 3)
    - Leadership Development Program (PA 68-338) -- 1971-1972 Season -- General Office Correspondence (Box 3)
    - New York Office Administration Correspondence and Information, 1971-1972 Season -- General Information Sent Representatives (Box 3)
    - New York Office Administration Correspondence and Information, 1971-1972 Season -- Fellowship Evaluation (Frank Logue) (Box 3)
    - New York Office Administration Correspondence and Information, 1971-1972 Season -- Job Description Project (Box 3)
    - New York Office Administration Correspondence and Information, 1971-1972 Season -- LDP Brochure, 1967 (Box 3)
    - New York Office Administration Correspondence and Information, 1971-1972 Season -- Procedures (Box 3)
    - New York Office Administration Correspondence and Information, 1971-1972 Season -- Spouse Travel Policy (Box 3)
    - New York Office Administration Correspondence and Information, 1971-1972 Season -- Miscellaneous Incl. Report Re: LDP (Box 3)
    - Northeast, 1972-1973 Season -- General Office Correspondence (Box 3)
    - Northeast, 1972-1973 Season -- Consultants (includes selection committee) (Box 3)
    - Northeast, 1973-1974 Season -- General Office Correspondence (Box 3)
    - Northeast, 1973-1974 Season -- Consultants and Selection Committee (Box 3)
    - Northeast, 1973-1974 Season -- Northeast Region -- IRI, 1971-1975 (Box 3)
    - Northeast -- General Office Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 3)
    - Closeout Folder -- Northeast Region, 1968-1973 (Box 3)
  - Northeast Region Peter Briggs Files, 1966-1970; I.3
    - Bohrson, Ralph, 1966-1967 (Box 4)
    - Bowdoin College, 1967 (Box 4)
    - Briggs, Henry Peter, 1967 (Box 4)
    - Briggs, Henry Peter, 1968 (Box 4)
    - Contacts and Advisors in All Three States, 1966 (Box 4)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 4)
    - Durnan, Vincent W. -- Vermont, 1967 (Box 4)
    - Dwelley, Marilyn -- Maine, 1967 (Box 4)
    - Educational Associations -- NASSP, 1966 (Box 4)
    - General Ford Foundation, 1966-1968 (Box 4)
    - Harvard University, 1966-1968 (Box 4)
    - Harvard University -- Special Admissions Project, 1970 (Box 4)
    - Hassfeld, Dorothy, 1968 (Box 4)
    - Joellen, Sister Mary -- New Hampshire, 1967-1968 (Box 4)
    - Meade, Edward Jr., 1966 (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 4)
    - Moll, C.L., 1967 (Box 4)
    - National Association of Educational Buyers, 1967 (Box 4)
    - New England Leadership Fellows Program (LPF), 1967 (Box 4)
    - New Hampshire, 1966-1967 (Box 4)
    - New Hampshire, University of, 1967 (Box 4)
    - Ragle, Barbara, 1967-1968 (Box 4)
    - Schwartz, Sister Mary Denis -- Maine, 1967 (Box 4)
    - Selection Committee, 1966 (Box 4)
    - Selection Committee -- December 7 Mailing to Selection Committee and November 22 Minutes, Candidates Statistics, 1966-1967 (Box 4)
    - Selection Committee -- January 3 Meeting Memoranda and Minutes, 1967 (Box 4)
    - Speeches and Projects, 1966 (Box 4)
    - Southeast-Southwest Leadership Fellows Program, 1967 (Box 4)
    - Southeast-Southwest Leadership Fellows Program -- Grant-Hassfeld, 1967 (Box 4)
    - Statistics -- December 16 List Re: LFP Fellows, 1966 (Box 4)
    - Vermont, 1967 (Box 4)
    - Wilson, Francis C. -- New Hampshire, 1967 (Box 4)
    - Applications, 1967 (Box 4)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Material is restricted from scholarly access - Personnel
- Southeast Region General Correspondence, 1968-1977; II
  - Southeast -- General Office Correspondence, 1968 (Box 5)
  - Southeast -- Consultants -- Formal and Informal, 1968-1969 (Box 5)
  - Southeast -- Staff, 1968 (Box 5)
  - Southeast -- Selection Committee, 1968 (Box 5)
  - Southeast -- General Office Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 5)
  - Southeast -- Consultants (Including Selection Committee), 1970-1971 (Box 5)
  - Southeast -- Staff, 1970-1971 (Box 5)
  - Southeast (Leadership Development Program, 1971-1972) -- General Correspondence (Box 5)
  - Southeast (Leadership Development Program, 1971-1972) -- Selection Committee Consultants (Box 5)
  - Southeast (Leadership Development Program, 1971-1972) -- Staff (Box 5)
  - Southeast (Leadership Development Program, 1971-1972) -- K.Z. Chavis -- Litigation [Confidential] (Box 5)
  - Southeast (1972-1973) -- General Office Correspondence (Box 5)
  - Southeast (1972-1973) -- Consultants and Selection Committee (Box 5)
  - Southeast (1972-1973) -- Staff (Box 5)
  - Southeast (1972-1973) -- Closeout Folder -- Southeast Region (Box 5)
  - Southeast (1972-1973) -- Post Fellowship Action (Box 5)
  - Southeast (1973-1974) -- Administrative Changeover 1973-1974 (Box 5)
  - Southeast (1973-1974) -- Administrative Changeover (Box 5)
  - Southeast (1973-1974) -- General Office Correspondence (Box 5)
  - Southeast (1973-1974) -- Consultants and Selection Committee (Box 5)
  - Southeast (1973-1974) -- Staff (Box 5)
  - Southeast (1973-1974) -- Fifth Southeast Region Leadership Development Program (LDP) Conference, Aug 7-12, 1973 (Box 5)
  - Southeast (1973-1974) -- LDP Fellows Conference -- Ramada Inn Airport -- Atlanta, GA (Box 5)
  - Southeast (1973-1974) -- Post Fellowship Meeting -- Alabama, Dec 7-9, 1973 (Box 5)
  - Southeast (1974-1975) -- Leadership University (Box 5)
  - Southeast (1974-1975) -- Consultants and Selection Committee (Box 5)
  - Southeast (1974-1975) -- General Office Correspondence (Box 5)
  - Southeast (1974-1975) -- Staff -- Administrative Changeover (Box 5)
  - Southeast -- Administrative Folders -- Mr. Bohrson Ada, Oct 19, 1977 (Box 5)
- Region-At-Large, 1969-1975; III
  - Region-at-Large -- General Office Correspondence, 1969 (Box 5)
  - Region-at-Large -- Correspondence Re: Fellows, 1969 (Box 5)
  - Region-at-Large -- Selection Committee, 1969 (Box 5)
  - Region-at-Large -- General Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 5)
  - Region-at-Large -- Selection Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 5)
  - Region-at-Large -- Staff, 1970-1971 (Box 5)
  - Region-at-Large -- General Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
  - Region-at-Large -- Selection Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
  - Region-at-Large -- Staff, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
  - Region-at-Large -- General Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 5)
  - Region-at-Large -- Selection Committee and Consultants, 1972-1973 (Box 5)
  - Region-at-Large -- Staff, 1972-1973 (Box 5)
  - Region-at-Large -- Closeout Folder, 1972-1973 (Box 5)
  - Region-at-Large -- General Office Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 5)
  - Region-at-Large -- Consultants and Selection Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 5)
  - Region-at-Large -- Staff, 1973-1974 (Box 5)
  - Region-at-Large -- Administrative Changeover, 1973-1974 (Box 5)
  - Region-at-Large -- Appalachia, 1973-1974 (Box 5)
  - Region-at-Large -- General Office Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 5)
  - Region-at-Large -- Staff, 1974-1975 (Box 5)
  - Office Inventory, 1974-1975 (Box 5)
- Miscellaneous, 1967-1974; IV
  - Miscellaneous -- A Report on the Mentor in the Leadership Fellow Program, Dec 29, 1967 (Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous -- Technical Memorandum, 1968 (Box 6)
  - Conferences -- June Fellow's Meeting, 1968 (Box 6)
  - Conferences -- Meeting of Fellows, 1969 (Box 6)
  - Conferences -- June Meeting, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Conferences -- All Fellows Conference -- Squaw Mountain Lodge, Jul 9-11, 1971 (Box 6)
  - Conferences -- New Fellows Meeting, Jun 9-10, 1972 (Box 6)
  - Conferences -- Fellows Conference, Aug 1972 (Box 6)
  - Conferences -- June Conference, 1973 (Box 6)
  - Conferences -- Indian Conference, 1973 (Box 6)
  - Conferences -- All Fellows Conference, 1973 (Box 6)
  - Programming -- Notes to Mentors, 1967-1968 (Box 6)
  - Programming -- Notes to Winners, 1967-1968 (Box 6)
  - Programming -- Notes to Current Winners, 1968-1969 (Box 6)
  - Programming -- Program Description, 1968 (Box 6)
  - Programming -- Winners and Mentors Addresses, 1967-1968 (Box 6)
  - Programming -- Brief on Proposed Fellow, 1968-1969 (Box 6)
  - Programming -- Goals, 1969-1970 (Box 6)
  - Programming -- Fellows Memorandum, 1969-1970 (Box 6)
  - Programming -- Statistics (fellows), 1969-1974 (Box 6)
  - Programming -- Newly Selected Fellows, 1971 (Box 6)
  - Programming -- Fellows Programming Materials, 1972-1973 (Box 6)
  - Programming -- Fellows Programming Materials, 1973-1974 (Box 6)
  - Recruiting -- Presidents of Local Teacher Associations, NH, VT and N.B., 1968 (Box 6)
  - Recruiting -- Contact for Recruiting, 1969 (Box 6)
  - Recruiting -- Letters to Superintendents, 1967-1968 (Box 6)
  - Recruiting -- Releases and Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 6)
  - Recruiting -- Maine Teachers Association, 1971 (Box 6)
  - Recruiting -- Recruiting Materials, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
  - Recruiting -- Application Materials, 1972-1973 (Box 6)
  - Recruiting -- Recruiting Materials, 1973-1974 (Box 6)
  - Selection -- On-Site Report, 1969 (Box 6)
  - Selection -- Interviews -- Candidates, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Selection -- Candidates, 1970-1971 (Box 6)
  - Selection -- St. Johnsbury Interviews, Feb 6-7, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Selection -- Fredericton Interviews, Apr 11, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Selection -- Farmington Interviews, Mar 28, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Selection -- On-Site Visits, 1970-1971 (Box 6)
  - Selection -- On-Site Visits, New Candidates, 1970-1971 (Box 6)
  - Selection -- Selection Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 6)
  - Selection -- Fredericton, N.B. Interviews, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
  - Selection -- Farmington, Me. Interviews, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
  - Selection -- St. Johnsbury, Vermont Interviews, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
  - Selection -- Fredericton Interviews, 1972-1973 (Box 6)
  - Selection -- St. Johnsbury Interviews, 1972-1973 (Box 6)
  - Selection -- Farmington Interviews, 1972-1973 (Box 6)
  - Selection -- Candidates -- "Questionnaires", 1972-1973 (Box 6)
  - Selection -- Selection Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 6)
  - Selection -- Selection Results, 1971-1974 (Box 6)
  - Selection -- Candidate Interview Schedule, 1973-1974 (Box 6)
- New York Office, 1967-1975; V
  - General Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 7)
  - LDP Forms Book, 1967-1968 (Box 7)
  - LDP Forms Book, 1968-1969 (Box 7)
  - LDP Forms Book, 1969 (Box 7)
  - LDP Forms Book, 1971 (Box 7)
  - LDP -- Northeast Region -- Program Descriptions, 1967-1970 (Box 7)
  - LDP -- Southeast Region -- Program Descriptions, 1967-1968 (Box 7)
  - LDP -- Southwest Region -- Program Descriptions, 1967-1969 (Box 7)
  - Douglas Derrer Reports, 1967-1972 (Box 7)
  - Leadership Development -- Review and Analysis of the First Year... D. Derrer, Nov 1971 (Box 7)
  - Douglas Derrer Activities, 1972-1973 (Box 7)
  - "Patterns of Mobility in Educational Leadership" - Doug Derrer Report, Apr 1973 (Box 7)
  - Computer Printouts -- Grants to Individuals, 1973-1974 (Box 8)
  - LDP DAP Budget, 1973-1974 (Box 8)
  - Drafts -- Grant Request, 1973-1974 (Box 8)
  - Selection Statistics, 1973 (Box 8)
  - Statistics -- Grant Request, 1973-1974 (Box 8)
  - LDP New York Office -- Miscellaneous, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - LDP New York Office -- LDP Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - LDP New York Office -- Weekly Approved Actions, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - LDP New York Office -- Staff, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - LDP New York Office -- Computer, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - LDP New York Office -- Inter Program Leadership Development, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - LDP New York Office -- General Information Sent Reps, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - LDP New York Office -- Insurance -- NYO, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - LDP New York Office -- Insurance #3, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - LDP New York Office -- LDP DAP Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - Review of Regional Offices -- General, 1973 (Box 8)
  - Review of Regional Offices -- Northeast Office, 1973-1974 (Box 8)
  - Review of Regional Offices -- Southwest Office, 1973-1974 (Box 8)
  - Review of Regional Offices -- Region at Large, 1973-1974 (Box 8)
  - IRS Tax Information -- New York Office -- Foundation Administration, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - IRS Tax Information -- New York Office -- Miscellaneous, 1973-1974 (Box 8)
  - IRS Tax Information -- New York Office -- Administrative Changeover -- General, 1973 (Box 8)
  - IRS Tax Information -- New York Office -- Status Reports -- Fellows, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - IRS Tax Information -- New York Office -- Sample Copies of Modification Letters, 1973 (Box 8)
  - IRS Tax Information -- New York Office -- 1099 File, 1973 (Box 8)
  - IRS Tax Information -- New York Office -- Staff, 1973 (Box 8)
  - IRS Tax Information -- New York Office -- LDP -- Meetings, 1973 (Box 8)
  - IRS Tax Information -- New York Office -- Periodic Reports of Approved Grants to Individuals, 1973-1974 (Box 8)
  - IRS Tax Information -- New York Office -- Accounting Codes -- Expense Classifications, 1973 (Box 8)
  - IRS Tax Information -- New York Office -- New York Office -- Publicity, 1973-1975 (Box 8)
  - IRS Tax Information -- New York Office -- Procedures for Grants to Individuals, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - IRS Tax Information -- New York Office -- Tax Information -- Fellows, 1973-1974 (Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous Reports -- Douglas Derrer, 1969-1970 (Box 9)
  - LDP -- Forms and Procedures, 1967-1969 (Box 9)
  - Leadership Development Program -- Inception and Development, 1968-1969 (Box 9)
  - LFP -- Tax Information, 1968-1969 (Box 9)
  - New York Office -- Administrative -- Correspondence and Information, 1968-1970 (Box 9)
  - New York Office -- Administrative -- Correspondence and Information, 1968-1969 (Box 9)
  - Northeast -- General Office Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 9)
  - Published Information on LDP, 1968 (Box 9)
  - Attachment Folder, 1972 (Box 9)
  - LDP Evaluation, 1968-1969 (Box 9)
  - Materials Sent to Regional Representatives, 1968-1969 (Box 9)
  - Payment of LDP Fellowship Funds to Non-Fellows, 1974 (Box 9)
  - Post Fellowship Supplements Insurance, 1974 (Box 9)
  - New York Office General Correspondence, 1974 (Box 9)
  - LDP Publicity, 1974-1975 (Box 9)
  - LDP General Correspondence, 1974 (Box 9)
  - Lists of LDP Fellows -- All Regions, 1972 (Box 9)
  - Indian Program, 1973-1974 (Box 9)
- Southwest Region, 1968-1975; VI
  - Southwest -- General Office Correspondence, 1968 (Box 10)
  - Southwest -- Consultants, 1968 (Box 10)
  - Southwest -- Selection Committee, 1968 (Box 10)
  - Southwest -- Correspondence Re: Fellows, 1967-1969 (Box 10)
  - Southwest -- Staff, 1968 (Box 10)
  - Southwest -- General Office Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 10)
  - Southwest -- General Office Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Southwest -- Consultants (incl. Selection Committee), 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Southwest -- Staff, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Southwest -- General Office Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 10)
  - Southwest -- Consultants (incl. Selection Committee), 1971-1972 (Box 10)
  - Southwest -- Staff, 1971-1972 (Box 10)
  - Southwest -- Closeout Folder, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Southwest -- Post-Fellowship -- Little, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Southwest -- General Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Southwest -- Consultants (incl. Selection Committee), 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Southwest -- Staff, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Southwest -- General Office Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
  - Southwest -- Staff, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
  - Southwest -- Consultants and Selection Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
  - Southwest -- Administrative Changeover, 1974 (Box 11)
  - Southwest -- General Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 11)
    - Appendix A: Reports, 1971
      - Bohrson, Ralph, Brenda Newman and Joshua Smith; Leadership Development Program -- Staff Paper, Nov 10, 1971 (Report #019967)
      - Bohrson, Ralph G. and Paul A. Judkins, Jr.; Thoughts on Future Northeast Leadership Development Program, Nov 12, 1971 (Report #019969)
      - Nachigal, Paul and Francis Parkman; The Comprehensive School Improvement Program, Jan 1971 (Report #019966)
  - Southwest -- Consultant and Selection Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 11)
  - Southwest -- Staff, 1974-1975 (Box 11)